But one last thing, because
that was one case that I
saw,
What is your favorite, most
interesting case that you've
seen?
Okay.
There's a guy, he actually
runs one of the country
up here, and he was, I think
he'll be okay with me
telling his story, but he
bachelor with a group of
guys
on a guy's trip in
Nashville, and he got hit by
driver, and he got his arm
crushed.
destroyed, and he was at
Vanderbilt Medical Center,
he said you could get
emergency
surgery here, or there's a
friend of mine who lives in
Palm Beach who you could
come
and go see, and ironically
it was me, and he had
looked it up and made an
appointment
and came in, and this guy
said it was meant to be.
He flew back, and he had
probably one of the most
difficult, blasted elbows
you've
ever seen, and he had nerve
damage, severe nerve damage,
and imagine he's a country
club manager does everything
and he's actually worked
with Tiger Woods and so a
really great
human being who really
didn't ask for this to
A year later, so we went
through a single surgery,
surgery didn't heal, still
had
nerve damage severe, the
most optimistic guy I've
met.
We took him back for a
revision surgery and six
later back he's back.
He has full function back,
he got his nerve damage
turned around with the
revision surgery
which he never thought would
happen.
Six months he waited
nothing.
And now he's got his full
elbow function.
And he sort of said, you
know, we joke,
but we gave him his life
back.